<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Explore -->
    <string name="error_explore_no_internet">No internet connection. Please check your network and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_explore_validation">The information you entered is invalid. Please review and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_explore_server">Something went wrong while exploring. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="error_explore_unknown">An unexpected error occurred. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_explore_timeout">The request took too long to respond. Please try again in a moment.</string>
    <string name="error_explore_too_many">You\'re making requests too quickly. Please slow down and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_explore_unrecognized">We couldn\'t understand the data. Try refreshing later.</string>
    <string name="error_explore_not_found">We couldn\'t find what you\'re looking for in Explore.</string>

    <!-- Series -->
    <string name="error_series_no_internet">No internet connection. Couldn\'t load series.</string>
    <string name="error_series_timeout">Loading series took too long. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="error_series_redirect">We had trouble reaching the series. Try again.</string>
    <string name="error_series_client">Something went wrong with the series request. Please retry.</string>
    <string name="error_series_server">Series server is currently unavailable. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="error_series_serialization">We couldn\'t load the series data correctly. Try refreshing.</string>
    <string name="error_series_not_found">This series couldn\'t be found.</string>
    <string name="error_series_validation">Some series data was invalid. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_series_corrupt_db">Something went wrong with local series data. Please restart the app.</string>
    <string name="error_series_disk">Your device couldn\'t access series files. Check your storage.</string>
    <string name="error_series_unknown">Something unexpected happened while loading the series.</string>

    <!-- Movies -->
    <string name="error_movies_network">There was a network problem while trying to load movies. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="error_movies_invalid_key">We couldn\'t connect to the movie service. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="error_movies_not_found">The movie you\'re looking for isn\'t available.</string>
    <string name="error_movies_server">Movie service is currently down. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="error_movies_unknown">An unexpected error occurred while loading movies.</string>

    <!-- Default -->
    <string name="error_default">Something went wrong. Please try again later.</string>
</resources>
